♪
Hey, what'd you guys get for number two?
嘿，你们第二题答案是什么？
- I got four. - I drew a head.
- 我选了四。 - 我画了个头。
Well, my life is officially over.
好吧，我的生活正式结束了。
My whole class saw... "it."
全班都看到了...那个。
[all gasp]
[所有人都惊讶]
But you've always been so careful with it.
但你一直都很小心对待它。
And always made sure to hide it.
而且总是确保藏好它。
And yet, there it was.
然而，它就在那里。
[laughs]
[笑]
You carry around a stuffed animal?
你随身带着一个毛绒玩具？
[laughter]
[笑声]
Lieutenant Blue Beary is not just a stuffed animal.
蓝熊中尉不仅仅是一个毛绒玩具。
[scoffs]
[嗤之以鼻]
I mean... no.
我的意思是...不。
[laughter]
[笑声]
So that's it. I'm giving up Blue Beary.
所以就这样了。我要放弃蓝熊中尉。
Yeah, right. He's helped you get straight As on every test since pre-K.
是啊，没错。自从幼儿园前，他帮你每次考试都得了全A。
You can't give him up.
你不能放弃他。
Well, I can give him up easier than you can give up
嗯，我放弃他比你放弃洗澡时带着你的小橡皮鸭要容易。
taking a bath with your little rubber duck.
和你的小橡皮鸭一起洗澡。
I don't need to take a bath with Ducky,
我不需要和Ducky一起洗澡，
I choose to.
我选择这样做。
I enjoy our talks.
我喜欢我们的对话。
You talk to him like this,
你这样和他说话，
"Quack, quack, quack, quack."
“嘎，嘎，嘎，嘎。”
Yeah. He's a duck.
是的。他是一只鸭子。
And what about you, Mitten Man?
那你呢，Mitten Man？
You still sleep with your baby mittens on your fingers
你还睡觉时把婴儿手套戴在手指上
and then rub your cheeks and your earlobes. - I don't rub the lobes anymore.
然后揉你的脸颊和耳垂。 - 我不再揉耳垂了。
Just the cheeks.
- Lobes and cheeks?
What did I walk in on?
[sighs] These guys still have their security items
from when they were babies.
Kids.
Oh, you mean, security thingies
like this?
That is a sweat towel for soccer.
Then why does it say, "Dawn's Blanky?"
Hey, guys,
嘿，伙计们，
your childhood security items are nothing to be embarrassed about.
你们小时候的安全物品没什么好尴尬的。
When I was a kid,
我小时候，
I had a Princess Suzie doll
我有一个苏西公主娃娃，
until one day she was sunbathing,
直到有一天她在晒太阳，
and my dad ran her over with our lawn mower.
我爸爸用我们的割草机把她碾过去了。
She was always there for me.
她总是陪在我身边。
[sobs] But I wasn't there for her!
但我没能在她需要时陪着她！
[singsongy] Issues.
问题啊。
[sighs] Wow.
哇。
Glad I'm not that attached to Blanky.
很高兴我对小毯子没有那么依赖。
What do you mean?
你什么意思？
You couldn't go a day without Blanky.
你一天都离不开小毯子。
And you three couldn't go an hour
而你们三个连一小时都离不开你们的小安全物件。
without your little security thingies.
要不要让这变得有趣点？
Care to make it interesting?
谁能最长时间不碰自己的熊、鸭子、毯子或手套，
Whoever can go the longest without their bear, duck,
谁就可以让其他人替他做一个月的家务。
blanket or mittens gets to have the others do their chores
谁参加？
for a month.
轻松。
Who's in?
准备好做我的家务吧，失败者们。
[scoffs] Easy.
[嘲笑声]简单。
Get ready to do my chores, losers.
准备好替我做家务吧，输家们。
You mean mine.
你是说我的。
[sighs] You don't stand a chance.
[叹气]你们一点机会都没有。
The contest is on.
比赛开始了。
Or should I say Quadtest.
或者我应该说是四人挑战赛。
I was just gonna say that!
我正想说那个！
Dang it!
可恶！
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪
[旋律吹口哨]
[whistling melody]
♪ ♪
[rhythmic clapping] ♪ One, two, three, four ♪
[whistling melody]
♪ ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na-na ♪
- ♪ One, two ♪ - ♪ Na, na, na ♪
- ♪ One, two, three, four ♪ - ♪ Na, na-na ♪
[upbeat music]
- Okay, your mother and I will keep your security items
好的，你妈妈和我将会保管你的安全物品
in this locked trunk for the duration of the Quadtest,
在这个上锁的箱子里，直到Quadtest结束，
and we'll check on them every day to make sure there's no cheatsies.
我们每天都会检查，确保没有作弊。
Oh, you've had these things since you were babies,
哦，这些物品从你们还是婴儿时就有了，
so if at any point, you want them back,
所以如果任何时候，你们想要回它们，
you just come and ask one of us.
只需要来向我们中的任何一个提出。
But you will be eliminated.
但你会被淘汰。
- Any point, just ask. - Eliminated.
任何时候，只要问。
- They get it, Tom.
他们会理解的，Tom。
They hired me to be tough, Anne.
他们雇我来就是要严格，Anne。
No one hired you.
没人雇你。
You followed us up here.
是你跟着我们上来的。
Just open the trunk.
打开后备箱吧。
Fine.
好吧。
- So long, Lefty and Righty.
再见，左撇子和右撇子。
Thanks for warming my hands
谢谢你们温暖我的手
and my heart.
和我的心。
[kisses] You be good, now.
亲吻 你要乖哦。
[sighs]
叹气
You were always there for me, Blanky.
你一直都在我身边，Blanky。
Now it's time for me to tuck you in.
现在轮到我来给你盖好被子了。
Sweet dreams.
祝你做个好梦。
Be brave.
要勇敢哦。
Quack, quack, quack? Quack.
嘎嘎嘎？嘎。
You've served me well, Lieutenant.
你一直为我尽心服务，中尉。
At ease.
放松点。
♪ And I--I ♪
♪ 而我——我 ♪
- Stop it. - I'm sorry.
- 别这样。- 对不起。
I'm just so sad.
我只是太难过了。
[sighs]
[叹气]
- Who wants soup? - Yeah, let's go. - Yeah. - Soup sounds good.
- 谁想喝汤？ - 好，走吧。 - 好。 - 汤听起来不错。
- I'm actually pretty proud of them.
- 我其实挺为他们骄傲的。
It's hard to let go of things.
放下一些事情很难。
Yeah.
是啊。
You know, maybe we should let go of a few things.
你知道，也许我们应该放下一些东西。
[chuckles] This is a mess.
[轻笑] 这真是一团糟。
Ooh.
哦。
Well, how about we start by getting rid of that old noise box?
好吧，我们何不从扔掉那个旧噪音盒开始？
Maybe there's a different old noise box that needs to be gotten rid of.
也许有另一个旧噪音盒需要被扔掉。
Tom.
汤姆。
What? I mean that one over there.
什么？我是说那边那个。
I use Squeezie all the time.
我经常用Squeezie。
[plays discordant chord]
[弹出不和谐的和弦]
Jeez. The last time you used that thing was for your failed Italian wedding band, That's Tom-more.
天哪。你上次用那东西是为了你失败的意大利婚礼乐队，那是Tom-more。
[coughs]
[咳嗽]
I would not say failed.
我不会说是失败的。
We booked two weddings and one very meshugenah bar mitzvah.
我们预订了两场婚礼和一个非常疯狂的犹太成人礼。
Uh-huh.
嗯哼。
But since you want to get rid of stuff,
但既然你想清理东西，
how about your old waffle maker?
那你的旧华夫饼机怎么样？
Well, how about...
好吧，那么...
this ridiculous motorcycle getup?
这件荒唐的摩托车装备怎么样？
Let's not be throwing "ridiculous" around
我们别随便用'荒唐'这个词
when you still have a hair crimper.
当你还留着烫发夹的时候。
Hey, crimping's coming back, dude.
嘿，烫发风潮又要回来了，伙计。
Don't-- [plays note]
别——[弹奏音符]
This is mine. Seriously, Tom?
这是我的。说真的，汤姆？
You're hurting Squeezie.
你弄疼Squeezie了。
♪ ♪
- Nicky, we're all waiting in the car.
- Nicky，我们都在车里等着呢。
We're gonna be late for school.
我们上学要迟到了。
- I'm up. I'm up.
- 我起来了，我起来了。
I'm just doing some close-eyed thinking
我只是在闭眼思考
about how you're gonna be doing all my chores.
关于你将如何完成我所有的家务。
Or were you having trouble last night sleeping
还是说你昨晚睡觉时
without your little baby mittens?
没有你的小宝宝手套就睡不好？
You know what would fix that?
你知道什么能解决这个问题吗？
Your little baby mittens.
你的小宝宝手套。
It's only a matter of time, Nicky.
这只是时间问题，Nicky。
[singsongy] ♪ You know you want them ♪
♪ 你知道你想要它们 ♪
Nice try, Dawn, but I'm not gonna cave.
不错的尝试，Dawn，但我不会屈服。
I'm totally fine.
我完全没问题。
♪ ♪
Aw, dude,
哇，伙计，
you reek.
你臭气熏天。
I don't know what you're talking about.
我不知道你在说什么。
I'm talking about you being afraid to have a bath
我说的是你害怕在没有小鸭子的情况下洗澡
without your duck.
不，我是问“臭气熏天”是什么意思？
No, I meant what does "reek" mean?
哦。
Oh.
Hey, Molly,
嘿，莫莉，
look, I might be bad at math,
看，我可能在数学上不太行，
but one thing I do know is,
但我确实知道一件事，
you and I add up.
你和我加起来正好。
[sniffs]
You reek.
你臭气熏天。
What is this, Make Up a Word Day?
这是什么，造词日吗？
It means you stink.
意思是说你很臭。
[sniffs]
Ooh. That's got to sting.
哦，那可真伤人。
[gasps] Release the quacken.
[倒抽气] 释放鸭怪。
Quack, quack.
嘎，嘎。
[woman] All righty, everyone,
[女士] 好了，各位，
I hope you came prepared.
希望你们都准备好了。
Good luck on your tests.
祝你们考试顺利。
[Ricky voice-over] All right, you do do this.
[瑞奇旁白] 好吧，你们确实要这么做。
It's not like Lieutenant Blue Beary took the tests.
又不是蓝熊上尉参加了考试。
You did.
是你们参加了。
Now just sharpen your pencil and breathe.
现在就削尖你的铅笔，深呼吸。
[pencil sharpener whirring]
[削铅笔声]
[crunching]
[咀嚼声]
Don't panic! Calm down.
不要慌！冷静下来。
You can do this.
你可以做到的。
Okay, name. Easy.
好的，名字。简单。
Ricky Blue Beary-- No!
Ricky Blue Beary——不！
Ahh!
啊！
[Dicky] Hey, Ricky,
[Dicky]嘿，Ricky，
it's me, Lieutenant Blue Beary.
是我，Lieutenant Blue Beary。
Admit it, you need--
承认吧，你需要——
Ow. Paper cut.
哎哟。纸割伤了。
[woman] All right, Harper,
好的，哈珀，
You've been playing really well lately.
你最近表现得很出色。
I'm thinking about starting you.
我考虑让你首发。
Let's see what you got.
让我看看你的实力。
Bring it on, Coach.
来吧，教练。
[whistle blows]
（哨声响起）
[Dawn voice-over] Whoo.
（黎明旁白）哇。
Here we go, Dawn.
开始了，黎明。
You don't need Blanky.
你不需要小毯子。
Just focus and-- whoa.
集中注意力，然后——哇。
That came in hot.
那球来得太快了。
Ah, come on.
哎呀，别这样。
You got this.
你能行的。
That came in hotter!
这球来得更猛！
Blanky, I need you!
毯子，我需要你！
Ahh!
啊！
[whistle blows]
（哨声）
What happened, Dawn?
怎么了，Dawn？
Jordan, get in here.
Jordan，进来。
Good thing you're just the backup.
还好你只是个替补。
♪ ♪
[door squeaks]
[门吱吱作响]
Well, somebody's looking good.
嗯，有人看起来不错。
Oh, you like my hair?
哦，你喜欢我的头发吗？
[chuckles] You leathered.
[轻笑] 你皮革化了。
You crimped.
你卷曲了。
Hey, you left your phone out.
嘿，你把手机落在外面了。
Might want to put that in your pocket.
可能想把它放进口袋里。
Ah, of course.
啊，当然。
That's where phones go. [strains]
那是放手机的地方。[用力]
Ah ha.
啊哈。
[strains]
[用力]
[ring tone sounding]
[铃声响起]
Aren't you gonna get that?
你不接吗？
No. I'm just gonna press ignore.
不，我按忽略。
[ringtone stops]
[铃声停止]
[woman on phone] Tommy, is that you?
[电话中的女人] 汤米，是你吗？
- Hi, Mom. - [chuckles]
- 嗨，妈妈。 - [轻笑]
[woman on phone] Is that Anne's laugh I hear?
[电话中的女人] 我听到的是安妮的笑声吗？
Ah, ah, why yes, it is Annie's laugh you hear.
啊，啊，是的，你听到的是安妮的笑声。
Annie,
安妮，
why don't you come and say hi to mother?
你不过来跟妈妈打个招呼吗？
Hi, Trish.
嗨，特里什。
[Trish] Did you get the sweaters I sent for the kids?
[特里什] 我寄给孩子们的毛衣收到了吗？
- Ooh. - Uh, yeah.
- 噢。- 嗯，收到了。
I did. Listen, we may lose you.
听着，我们可能要失去信号了。
Ouch!
哎哟！
I think the waffles are done.
我想华夫饼做好了。
Oh.
哦。
It's a professional, fully functioning waffle maker, Tom.
这是一个专业、功能齐全的华夫饼机，汤姆。
- Hmm. - It'll ding when it's done.
- Sure. - Mm-hmm.
Ding! Ooh. There it is.
[all arguing]
Hey, hey, kids.
How's the old Quadtest going?
Well, I feel great without my Blanky.
And I haven't thought twice about that bear.
And Dicky, we can all smell how you're doing.
What are you talking about? I smell fine.
If I smelled bad, I'd take a bath.
如果我闻起来不好，我会洗澡。
Hi, boy.
嗨，小子。
[dog whimpering]
[狗呜咽]
[dog barks]
[狗吠]
[humming]
[哼唱]
I'm out!
我退出！
both: What?
什么？
I'm out of the Quadtest.
我退出Quadtest。
Sweet!
太好了！
You dropped out 'cause of the website.
你因为那个网站退出了。
What website?
什么网站？
Dude,
伙计，
you fell asleep so much at school yesterday,
你昨天在学校睡得那么多，
kids started taking pictures of you.
孩子们开始给你拍照。
And posting them on PutStuffOnNicky.com
还把照片上传到PutStuffOnNicky.com
I dropped out 'cause lack of sleep is unhealthy.
我退赛是因为睡眠不足对健康不利。
[gasps]
（吸气声）
This is terrible!
这太糟糕了！
And then there were three.
然后就剩下三个人了。
Soon to be just me.
很快就会只剩下我一个。
I'm not gonna rhyme,
我不会押韵，
but you guys should take me very serious...ly.
但你们应该非常认真地对待我...
Oh, I did rhyme!
哦，我押韵了！
♪ ♪
[school bell rings]
[学校铃声响起]
Ricky, can I talk to you a minute?
Ricky，我能和你谈一会儿吗？
So I graded your test
我批改了你的试卷
and for the first time ever,
而且是有史以来第一次，
I had to use...
我不得不使用...
the red pen.
红色笔。
[gasps]
[倒吸一口气]
You know, your brother bit a hole in his test
你知道吗，你哥哥在他的试卷上咬了个洞，
and he got a better grade than you.
他的分数比你还要高。
[gasps louder]
[更加大声地倒吸一口气]
You know that this test is worth 50% of your grade, right?
你知道这次考试占你总成绩的50%，对吧？
Yes, I do.
是的，我知道。
Well, you know what? Since you're normally such a good student,
那么，你知道吗？既然你平时成绩一直很好，
I'm going to let you retake it.
我允许你重考一次。
[gasps] Thank you, Mrs. Harvell!
[倒吸一口气] 谢谢您，哈维尔夫人！
But you only get one retake.
但是你只有一次重考的机会。
Okay, whatever grade you get this time
好吧，无论这次你得到什么成绩
is final.
都是最终成绩。
If I were you, bro,
如果我是你，兄弟，
I'd go back to the bear before you ruin your life.
我会在毁掉你的生活之前回到熊那里。
So, Dicky, I just found out we're gonna be lab partners.
所以，迪基，我刚刚发现我们要成为实验室伙伴。
Sweet! Lab partner hug.
太好了！实验室伙伴拥抱。
This is the problem,
这就是问题所在，
I want to be your lab partner,
我想成为你的实验室伙伴，
but until you stop smelling like a big bag of farts,
但直到你停止闻起来像一大袋屁，
that's not happening.
那是不可能的。
If I were you, bro,
如果我是你，兄弟，
I'd go back to the duck before you ruin your life.
我会在毁掉你的生活之前回到鸭子那里。
Beautiful morning, huh, guys?
美丽的早晨，对吧，伙计们？
Since I got Lefty and Righty back,
自从我找回了左撇子和右撇子，
life smells sweet. [sniffs]
生活闻起来很甜美。[嗅]
Gimme those.
给我那些。
I need to smell sweet.
我需要闻起来甜美。
Oh! You reek!
哦！你臭死了！
- Ow! My ankle.
哎哟！我的脚踝。
- Can you put any weight on it, Jordan?
- 你能承受重量吗，乔丹？
- [strains] No, I don't think so.
- [用力] 不行，我觉得不行。
Well, Harper, whatever was wrong with you in practice
好吧，哈珀，不管你在训练中出了什么问题
better get fixed by Friday.
最好在周五前解决。
You're starting against the Mustangs.
你要对战野马队首发。
Ooh, bad time to be in a contest, huh?
哦，这个时候比赛可不太妙，是吧？
I wish I had advice to help you play better,
我希望我能给你一些建议帮你打得更好，
but I'm drawing a Blanky.
但我现在脑子一片空白。
I also drew a Blanky.
我也一片空白。
You'd be a better goalie if you had your Bl--
如果你有你的Bl--，你会是个更好的守门员。
Ow! Same cut.
哎哟！同一个地方受伤了。
♪ ♪
[Anne] Okay, quadtestants,
[Anne] 好了，四项挑战者们，
who's ready for waffle burgers?
谁准备好迎接华夫饼汉堡了？
[quack]
[嘎嘎]
I'm out.
我退出了。
both: What?
两人：什么？
What happened?
发生了什么？
Two words:
两个词：
big bag of farts.
一大袋屁。
So I'm out of the the Quadtest,
所以我退出了Quadtest，
which means I'm in as Molly's new lab partner.
这意味着我将成为Molly的新实验室搭档。
Totally worth it.
完全值得。
And then there were two.
然后就剩下我们两个了。
Have fun doing my chores.
做我的家务活儿去吧。
We'll just see about that.
我们走着瞧。
Yeah, we--
是的，我们——
[Italian music playing]
[意大利音乐播放]
Do you guys hear that music?
你们听到那音乐了吗？
♪ ♪
[Tom] Bring it home. Bring it home.
带回家。带回家。
Yeah!
耶！
Whoo!
哇！
Tom.
汤姆。
- Hmm? - What's going on?
嗯？ - 怎么了？
Oh, I just got That's Tom-more back together.
哦，我刚把汤姆乐队重新组合起来了。
You remember Vito and Alfredo?
你还记得维托和阿尔弗雷多吗？
Steve, Lenny.
史蒂夫，伦尼。
Anyway, we'll be practicing our accordion-based music all night.
总之，我们今晚要练习我们的手风琴音乐。
Oh, why don't I throw a couple of waffle pizzas
哦，我为什么不给你烤几个华夫披萨呢？
in the oven for you?
放进烤箱给你烤几块华夫披萨怎么样？
Ah, pizza.
啊，披萨。
Gee, gentlemen,
哎呀，先生们，
that sounds nice.
听起来不错。
Two! Three! Four!
二！三！四！
all: ♪ A pizza, pizza, pizza, pizza ♪
♪ 披萨，披萨，披萨，披萨 ♪
♪ Pizza, pizza, pizza, pizza ♪
♪ Mangia, mangia ♪
♪ 吃吧，吃吧 ♪
♪ Love-a the pizza, yay ♪
♪ 爱这披萨，耶 ♪
♪ I love-a the pizza from here to San Jose ♪
♪ 我爱这披萨，从这里到圣何塞 ♪
♪ From Washington to Delaware ♪
♪ 从华盛顿到特拉华 ♪
♪ And all the way to Tampa Bay ♪
♪ 一直到达坦帕湾 ♪
♪ That's the way we eat the pizza ♪
♪ 这就是我们吃披萨的方式 ♪
all: ♪ In the U.S.A. ♪
♪ 在美国 ♪
[Tom] Oh, my.
哦，我的天。
♪ ♪
Worried about your super important,
担心你那超级重要、
make or break, potential life-ruining
决定成败、可能毁掉一生的
makeup test that's 50% of your grade?
化妆考试，占你成绩的50%？
I would be.
我会的。
No, but I bet you're worried about your big game tomorrow.
不，但我敢打赌你担心明天的重大比赛。
I heard the Mustangs are the highest scoring team
我听说野马队是科罗拉多州得分最高的球队
in Colorado.
那些女孩的大腿
Those girls have thighs
就像真正的野马一样。
like actual mustangs.
如果迪基的分数比你高，那不是很奇怪吗
Wouldn't it be weird if Dicky got a better grade than you
妈妈会把他的试卷贴在冰箱上而不是你的？
and Mom put his test on the fridge instead of yours?
不错的尝试，Dawn，
Nice try, Dawn,
但我不会动摇。
but I'm not gonna cave.
这只是一次考试。
It's just one test.
只是一次考试，嗯？
[Dawn] Just one test, huh?
就一次考试，是吗？
I wonder what celebrated science educator Science Bob
我想知道那位著名的科学教育家Science Bob
would say about failing just one test?
会怎么看待仅仅一次考试不及格？
[singsongy] Science Bob.
Science Bob。
Hello.
你好。
Celebrator science educator Science Bob?
那位庆祝科学教育的Science Bob？
What are you doing here?
你在这里做什么？
Ricky, your sister told me about your math test,
Ricky，你姐姐告诉我你的数学考试情况，
and I want you to know that I didn't become Science Bob
我想让你知道，我成为Science Bob
by taking just one test for granted,
并不是把一次考试当作儿戏，
especially one that was 50% of my grade.
尤其是那个占了你成绩50%的考试。
So you got to think about your future, Ricky,
所以你要考虑你的未来，Ricky，
and don't waste it over some silly competition.
不要因为一些愚蠢的竞争而浪费它。
Wake the bear.
唤醒熊。
That's really good advice.
那真是很好的建议。
I really appreciate it.
我真的很感激。
No problem.
没事。
Now, on to more important things.
现在，谈点更重要的事情。
Uh, where are your Stair Climbers?
呃，你的楼梯机呢？
I'm thinking about becoming a slightly hunkier Bob.
我在考虑成为一个稍微更健壮的Bob。
Up the stairs to the left.
在楼梯左边。
Up the...stairs.
上...楼梯。
Uh, yeah. Never mind.
呃，是的。没关系。
That was cute, Dawn,
那很可爱，Dawn，
but Science Bob isn't the only one with good advice.
但科学Bob不是唯一一个给出好建议的人。
There's someone here who would like to talk to you.
这里有个人想和你谈谈。
Alex!
Alex！
Alex Morgan? No way!
Alex Morgan？不可能！
Hey, Dawn.
嘿，Dawn。
Rick emailed me about your big game tomorrow
Rick给我发了邮件，说你明天的重大比赛
and how you'd rather let your team down
而不是让你的团队失望
than lose the Quadtest.
而不是输掉Quadtest。
I--well, it's a little more complicated than that, but--
我——嗯，事情比那复杂一点，但是——
You think I made it to the U.S. Women's National Team
你认为我通过让我的队友失望
by letting my teammates down?
才进入美国女子国家队的吗？
I'm gonna guess no.
我猜不是。
Good answer, Rick. Make the right play, Dawn.
好答案，Rick。做出正确的选择，Dawn。
Speaking of plays,
说到比赛，
have you guys seen Science Bob?
你们见过Science Bob吗？
He was supposed to take me to see Wicked.
他本来说要带我去看《魔法坏女巫》。
Without Blanky,
没有小毯子，
you'll tanky.
你会崩溃的。
Nice try, but it didn't work.
尝试不错，但没成功。
- I'm still not gonna cave! - Me neither!
- 我还是不会屈服！ - 我也是！
Excuse me, where can I find your T-ball bats?
打扰一下，请问你们的T球棒在哪里？
- Oh-- [boy screams]
- 哦—— [男孩尖叫]
Excuse me, can you do me a favor?
打扰一下，能帮我个忙吗？
[Trish on phone] Tommy, what's wrong?
[Trish在电话中] Tommy，怎么了？
[clears throat] Nothing, Mom!
[清嗓子] 没事，妈妈！
I just butt-dialed you.
我只是不小心拨了你的电话。
I'm gonna hang up now.
我现在要挂电话了。
Can you just press my right cheek?
你能帮我按一下我的右脸颊吗？
It's not what you're-- I just have a hard time hanging up with my Mom.
不是你想的那样——我只是很难挂断和我妈妈的电话。
Mom, can we go to Get Sporty-er?
妈妈，我们可以去Get Sporty-er吗？
Okay, this has gone too far.
好吧，这已经太过分了。
We're scaring customers.
我们在吓跑顾客。
You win, you made your point.
你赢了，你已经表达了你的观点。
You can keep your accordion and your leathers.
你可以保留你的手风琴和皮衣。
I'm not making a point, Anne, I'm--
我不是在表达观点，安妮，我——
I'm stuck.
我卡住了。
This leather's so tight, it's fused with my body.
这件皮衣太紧了，它已经和我的身体融为一体。
I can't tell where leather stops and Tom begins.
我都分不清皮衣在哪里结束，汤姆从哪里开始。
Then why are you carrying your accordion?
那你为什么还带着你的手风琴？
It's stuck to my zipper. I'm a wreck, Anne!
它卡在我的拉链上了。我一团糟，安妮！
Me too, Tom.
我也是，汤姆。
Our entire house smells like burnt hair and charred waffles.
我们整个房子闻起来像烧焦的头发和烤焦的华夫饼。
I'll throw away my attic trash if you do.
如果你扔掉，我就扔掉我的阁楼垃圾。
Deal.
成交。
[both sigh]
（两人叹气）
[accordion plays chord] Oh, come on.
（手风琴奏出和弦）哦，拜托。
♪ ♪
[exhales]
（呼气声）
[dog barks]
（狗叫声）
What?
什么？
I can't let my teammates down.
我不能让我的队友失望。
I'm just gonna borrow Blanky for the Mustang game
我只是借用一下Blanky去参加野马队的比赛，
and put her back before anyone finds out.
并在任何人发现之前还回去。
[exhales]
（呼气声）
Ahh!
啊！
This is not what it looks like.
这不是看起来那样的。
Looks like you cheated.
看起来你作弊了。
You can't prove that!
你无法证明这一点！
You're in the trunk holding the bear.
你正抱着熊坐在后备箱里。
How do you know he's not holding me?
你怎么知道他不是抱着我？
You're eliminated!
你被淘汰了！
Yes!
太好了！
It doesn't matter. You cheated too!
这无关紧要。你也作弊了！
You're eliminated.
你被淘汰了。
All right, fine.
好吧，好吧。
Either we're both eliminated,
要么我们都淘汰，
or...
或者...
you take Blue Beary,
你拿蓝熊，
and I take Blanky, we use them tomorrow and
我拿毯子，我们明天用它们然后
put them back without Nicky and Dicky ever finding out.
放回去，不让尼基和迪基发现。
I would say we never said any of this.
我觉得我们从未说过这些。
Said any of what?
说过什么？
Just to be clear,
只是为了明确，
we are making a deal right now, right?
我们现在是在做交易，对吧？
Yes.
对。
Now, let's get you out of there.
现在，让我们把你弄出来。
[door creaks open]
[门吱吱作响地打开]
Or you in here!
或者你进来了！
[dog barks]
[狗叫]
Shh!
嘘！
I threw everything else away.
我把其他东西都扔掉了。
I just couldn't cut the chord.
我就是割不断那根弦。
Okay. Here we go.
好了。我们开始吧。
What's he doing?
他在做什么？
Shh! Just stay quiet.
嘘！保持安静。
Huh.
嗯。
I thought I locked this.
我以为我锁上了。
Come on, buddy.
加油，伙计。
What was that?
那是什么声音？
Dad's going down the stairs.
爸爸正下楼梯。
No, the click before that.
不，是之前的咔嗒声。
Oh, that.
哦，那个啊。
He totally locked us in.
他完全把我们锁在里面了。
[banging on trunk]
[敲打后备箱]
Okay, don't panic.
好了，别慌。
I know exactly what to do.
我知道该怎么做。
Somebody help! We're stuck in here!
有人来帮帮忙！我们被困在这里了！
Help!
救命！
[muffled shouting]
（模糊的呼喊声）
[Ricky] Get your butt out of my face!
（瑞奇）把你的屁股从我脸上挪开！
[Dawn] Get your face out of my butt!
（道恩）把你的脸从我屁股上挪开！
[muffled shouting and banging]
（模糊的呼喊声和敲打声）
- What is that noise?
那是什么声音？
[banging]
（敲打声）
[strains]
（用力声）
[both groaning]
（两人呻吟）
[singsongy] ♪ Hey, guys ♪
♪ 嘿，伙计们 ♪
This isn't what it looks like.
这不是看起来那样。
It looks like you're cheating.
看起来你是在作弊。
[gasps] Run!
哎呀！快跑！
Whoa!
哇！
[groans]
（呻吟）
Look at us.
看看我们。
What are we doing?
我们在做什么？
None of us won.
我们都没赢。
I mean, we couldn't last three days
我是说，我们连三天都撑不过去
without our bear, duck, blanket, or mittens.
没有我们的熊、鸭子、毯子或手套，我们连三天都撑不过去。
We obviously still need them.
我们显然还是需要它们的。
The Quadtest was a bad idea.
四重测试是个糟糕的主意。
Yeah, as long as our stuff makes us happy,
是啊，只要我们的东西能让我们开心，
who cares what other people think?
谁在乎别人怎么想呢？
- Yeah, you're right. - I agree.
- 是啊，你说得对。 - 我同意。
But let's still not tell other people.
但我们还是不要告诉别人。
- Yeah, yeah. - Totally.
- 对，对。 - 完全同意。
Who wants soup?
谁想喝汤？
[all] ♪ Soup, soup, soup, soup, soup, soup, soup, soup ♪
汤，汤，汤，汤，汤，汤，汤，汤
♪ I love-a soup from bisque to consommé ♪
♪ 我爱汤，从浓汤到清汤 ♪
♪ From navy bean to lima bean ♪
♪ 从海军豆到利马豆 ♪
♪ And every bean along the way ♪
♪ 以及沿途的每一种豆 ♪
♪ That's the way we eat the soup ♪
♪ 这就是我们吃汤的方式 ♪
♪ In the U.S.A ♪
♪ 在美国 ♪
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
[whistling melody]
[吹口哨的旋律]
♪ ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ 耶 ♪
♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ 是的 ♪
♪